<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Plant Doctor</string>
    <string name="text">Select the plant from below to identify the leaf disease</string>
    <string name="analyse">ANALYSE</string>
    <string name="contactus">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="help">HELP</string>
    <string name="about">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="about1"><b>The Leaf Doctor </b>app is a quantitative assessment tool for plant diseases.\nThis interactive app allows users to collect or submit photographs of symptomatic plant organs (e.g., leaves) and measure the percentage of tissue area diseased. The assessment data and photographs may be sent by e-mail to any recipient.\n\nFor more information, see:\nPlant Disease Detection by using Deep Learning algorithm research paper in International Journal of Recent Technology and Engineering(IJRTE) in year 2020. The writers of this paper is Murk Chohan and Adil khan.\n\n<h2><b>Instructions</b></h2>\n\n
    <h2><b>1. PHOTOGRAPHS.</b></h2>" The app's assessment algorithm is based on the user-guided recognition of pixel colors for healthy plant tissues. You may use your Android smartphone to take a photograph or analyze photographs already saved to your gallery. Leaves should be photographed individually against a solid black background, such as a black piece of paper or cloth. Alternately, a photograph may be modified using Adobe Photoshop or other software to create a black background to surround an individual leaf. Such photographs can be e-mailed to the app user, who saves it to their gallery for disease assessment via The Leaf Doctor. Take photographs under shade, such as that provided by a dark umbrella or a dense plant canopy. This will help to minimize reflected light on leaf surfaces that can complicate the app's disease measurement algorithm. Do not use a camera flash."\n
   <h2><b>2. ASSESSMENT.</b></h2>" Touch a healthy area within the photograph to begin a disease assessment. This specifies the color of healthy tissue. Pinch the screen with thumb and forefinger to enlarge the image for more precise selection of colors. You may select several different colors to represent the healthy areas by touching consecutive areas of the photograph that correspond to the healthy tissue. After removing the background (i.e., the black color), the algorithm analyzes the entire image, pixel by pixel, to determine the proximity of a pixel/'s color to the healthy color(s). The maximum distance from a healthy color can be adjusted by using the threshold slider. After you are satisfied with the result by visual inspection, the app computes the percentages of healthy and diseased pixels and displays the result."\n\n
    <h2><b>Uses of The Leaf Doctor:</b></h2>\n\nThe Leaf Doctor app may be used in the following ways:\n\n1. To quantify the progress of plant disease epidemics in space and/or time;\n2. To compare treatments used for plant disease management;
        \n3. To evaluate host resistance or to compare host varieties and environments for disease development;
       \n4. To develop standard area diagrams for plant disease assessment.\n\n<h2><b>Acknowledgements:</b></h2>\n\n"This project is developed by RKGIT, Ghaziabad students to help farmers of India. Support of this project is is provided by faculty of RKGIT. The main support of this project is provided by our guid Ms.Vernika singh ma'am"
    </string>
</resources>